http://hoganhansen.com/privacy-policy

Home /Privacy Policy
Legal DisclaimerThe Hogan - Hansen website is intended to provide general guidance and information only. Hogan - Hansen has not been engaged to perform legal, accounting, tax, auditing or consulting services. As such, information provided on this site should not be used as a substitute for consultation with professional advisors. Hogan - Hansen has made every effort to provide timely and accurate information; however, errors or omissions may occur. Hogan - Hansen will take no responsibility for any errors, omissions or for the results obtained from using the information provided. All information on this website is provided "as is," with no express or implied warranties.HK Alliance is a premier affiliation of independent accounting and business advisory firms. HK Alliance member firms maintain their name, autonomy and independence and are responsible for their own client fee arrangements, delivery of services and maintenance of client relationships. Each member company is a separate and independent legal entity and as such has no liability for the acts or omissions of any other member firm. HK Alliance, LLC provides no services to clients and has no liability for the acts or omissions of any member firm. The HK Alliance is an association and does not fall within the definition of “network” under the American Institute of Certified Public Accountants, Inc. (“AICPA”) Interpretation No. 26-2 and as may be further defined by federal or state laws or regulations. HK Alliance, LLC is an Iowa limited liability company affiliated with but separate from Honkamp Krueger Financial Services, Inc., an Iowa business corporation. HK, the HK logo and the HK Alliance signatures are used under license from HK Alliance, LLC.Privacy PolicyAt Hogan - Hansen, we want to provide you with the best possible web browsing experience. Part of that experience is the security in knowing that any information you give us will remain private. We go to great lengths to ensure your privacy within any given part of our site.Use of Personal InformationHogan - Hansen will not gather your personal information without your permission. We will not link your IP address to anything identifiable. All browsing on our site is done anonymously.If personal information is required for any reason, that information will be used solely by Hogan - Hansen and its business partners. This information can only be taken if you voluntarily choose to give it to us. At no time will we sell personal information, or make it otherwise available to any third-party companies. Hogan - Hansen reserves the right to use submitted personal information for marketing and promotional purposes.Some features within the Hogan - Hansen website may require personal information to log in or access those specific features. If you do not want to submit that information, those areas may be unavailable for use. We obtain this information only for safety and security reasons.While the content of our page is suitable for audiences of any age, no information should be submitted from those under the age of 18, without the consent of a parent or guardian.Adherence to GuidelinesIf you feel that Hogan - Hansen has not adhered to the above policy, please notify us, and we will work to determine the problem and correct it accordingly.
Accountants with Personality
About us
Accounting
Accounting & Auditing
Payroll & Bookkeeping
Income Tax Preparation
Consulting
Research & Development Tax Credits
©2020. Hogan - Hansen. All rights reserved. Site created and powered by VGM Forbin
